<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LangChain Project Handbook :: LangChain AI</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/j3ffyang/langchain_project_book/index.html</link>
    <description>Introduction My Journey with LangChain In late 2022, I embarked on an exciting journey with LangChain while leading a development team. This coincided with OpenAI’s significant boost in popularity, marking a pivotal moment in AI technology.&#xA;Discovery and Adoption After several months of exploration, our team identified LangChain as the ideal API standard and base platform for our projects. What drew us to LangChain was its comprehensive suite of features:</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:10:48 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/j3ffyang/langchain_project_book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Preface</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/j3ffyang/langchain_project_book/preface/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/j3ffyang/langchain_project_book/preface/index.html</guid>
      <description>It is with great pleasure and enthusiasm that I present to you this book on the orchestration of large language models with LangChain. As an experienced Python and LangChain developer, I have had the privilege of participating in numerous projects that revolve around language modeling. These engagements have provided me with invaluable hands-on experience and insight into the complexities and challenges associated with building and managing large language models.&#xA;The goal of this book is to equip you, the reader, with the knowledge and skills necessary to successfully orchestrate large language models using LangChain. We will explore the intricacies of language modeling, delve into the nuances of LangChain, and provide practical guidance on how to effectively manage and optimize language models at scale. This book aims to serve as your comprehensive guide, blending theory with real-world scenarios to offer a holistic understanding of this cutting-edge technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LangChain Fundamentals</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/j3ffyang/langchain_project_book/fundamentals/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 00:10:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/j3ffyang/langchain_project_book/fundamentals/index.html</guid>
      <description>The fundamental ideas and elements of LangChain, a framework for creating language-model-powered applications, are covered in this chapter. LangChain aims to develop data-aware and agentic applications that enable language models to communicate with their surroundings and establish connections with other data sources, rather than only calling out to a language model via an API.&#xA;At the heart of LangChain are two key components. The first one is the modular abstractions provided by LangChain, which are essential for working with language models. These components are designed to be easy to use, whether you use the rest of the LangChain framework or not.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>