<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LangChain Project Handbook :: LangChain AI</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/index.html</link>
    <description>My Journey with LangChain In late 2022, I embarked on an exciting journey with LangChain while leading a development team. This coincided with OpenAI’s significant boost in popularity, marking a pivotal moment in AI technology.&#xA;Discovery and Adoption After several months of exploration, our team identified LangChain as the ideal API standard and base platform for our projects. What drew us to LangChain was its comprehensive suite of features:&#xA;Configuring vector databases Orchestrating multiple popular embeddings and large language models from open source community Facilitating complex workflows with agents These capabilities made LangChain an indispensable tool for our development needs.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:39:33 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Preface</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/preface/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/preface/index.html</guid>
      <description>It is with great pleasure and enthusiasm that I present to you this book on the orchestration of large language models with LangChain. As an experienced Python and LangChain developer, I have had the privilege of participating in numerous projects that revolve around language modeling. These engagements have provided me with invaluable hands-on experience and insight into the complexities and challenges associated with building and managing large language models.&#xA;The goal of this book is to equip you, the reader, with the knowledge and skills necessary to successfully orchestrate large language models using LangChain.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LangChain Fundamentals</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/fundamentals/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 18:56:59 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/fundamentals/index.html</guid>
      <description>The fundamental ideas and elements of LangChain, a framework for creating language-model-powered applications, are covered in this chapter. LangChain aims to develop data-aware and agentic applications that enable language models to communicate with their surroundings and establish connections with other data sources, rather than only calling out to a language model via an API.&#xA;At the heart of LangChain are two key components. The first one is the modular abstractions provided by LangChain, which are essential for working with language models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tools and Libraries</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/tools_n_lib/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 20:44:50 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/tools_n_lib/index.html</guid>
      <description>This chapter provides a comprehensive guide on how to set up LangChain in a Python environment. It is essential to have a basic understanding and knowledge of Python as a prerequisite for this guide. The following steps will help you establish a robust Python environment tailored for LangChain development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Document Summarization</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/doc_sum/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:13:34 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/doc_sum/index.html</guid>
      <description>In the previous chapters, we discussed the key components and features of LangChain, along with instructions on setting up a development environment. Our next step involves integrating these elements into a practical case study.&#xA;Business Scenario Let’s say that there are numerous interconnected documents, sharing similar narratives within a specific domain such as sales strategies or human resource policies. The goal is to develop a bot capable of comprehending these documents and responding to user queries based on the information contained within.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ticketing System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:35:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/index.html</guid>
      <description>Our company undertakes a project to offer operational and support services to one of our banking clients. A key component of this effort is the “Ticketing System,” a tool utilized by the operation team to record all customer inquiries. This system encompasses a broad spectrum of issues, ranging from password resets to more complex matters such as operating system restoration and disk failure. Once a problem is identified, it is forwarded to the expert team for resolution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KnowledgeBase Semantic Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/knowledgebase_semantic_analysis/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 22:39:33 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/knowledgebase_semantic_analysis/index.html</guid>
      <description>A knowledge base acts as a centralized hub for all essential information, streamlining the organization and standardization of knowledge within a company. This not only enhances internal efficiency by providing employees with quick access to necessary details but also projects the company as modern, professional, and up-to-date. Moreover, it facilitates direct engagement with stakeholders, fostering a feedback loop that can significantly improve relationships and customer loyalty. By adopting a knowledge base, enterprises can significantly enhance their operational efficiency, reduce customer support costs through self-service solutions, and ultimately boost their overall business performance.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>