<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ticketing System on LangChain AI</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ticketing System on LangChain AI</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:35:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Technical Process</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/tech_proc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:18:01 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/tech_proc/</guid>
      <description>The technical process generally follows this sequence:&#xA;Load the CSV file. Embed the selected data into a vector database. Create a compression_retriever that I&amp;rsquo;ll introduce in details Perform a similarity_search. Generate a prompt based on previous conversations. Define a chain with source data using RetrievalQAWithSourcesChain Send the output to the LLM for semantic optimization. The following diagram illustrates the main work flow of the data processing.&#xA;file CSVLoader file embedding database vectorstore file base_retriever file compression_retriever file llm file result CSVLoader -&gt; embedding embedding -&gt; vectorstore vectorstore --&gt; base_retriever compression_retriever &lt;- base_retriever compression_retriever --&gt; llm: prompt llm -&gt; result Figure 5.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:20:49 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/architecture/</guid>
      <description>In this chapter, we continue to employ RAG for data retrieval from the vector database, followed by processing with the LLM. However, to enhance data retrieval efficiency, we introduce a new feature known as the Contextual Compression Retriever.&#xA;actor user package data_processing { agent CSVLoader agent embedding } package base_retriever { database vectorstore } package compression_retriever{ agent ContextualCompressionRetriever } note right of compression_retriever:Enhance the context \nquality and accuracy\nand reduce hallucination package augmented { agent prompt agent llm } CSVLoader -&gt; embedding embedding --&gt; vectorstore:insert selected data\ninto vectordb embedding --&gt; vectorstore:embed user&#39;s query user -&gt; embedding: query vectorstore --&gt; ContextualCompressionRetriever ContextualCompressionRetriever --&gt; prompt:compression_retriever.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM with GPT4All</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/llm_with_gpt4all/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:23:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/llm_with_gpt4all/</guid>
      <description>This time, we&amp;rsquo;re leveraging Mistral in GGUF format, which is compatible with CPU execution. The model is packaged by GPT4All. From GPT4All official website, it says that GPT4All is:&#xA;A free-to-use, locally running, privacy-aware chatbot. No GPU or internet required.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s open-source as well. To understand GPT4All better, you can get more information from https://gpt4all.io. We just download the model from GPT4All and utilize it with LangChain. The model can be downloaded onto anywhere on your computer and it&amp;rsquo;s operating system independent.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Processing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/data_processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:25:50 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/data_processing/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the data schema of CSV again. Its structure is&#xA;ticket_number,date,caller,application,query,responder,solution,timestamp In this business scenario, we possess a substantial volume of data from call center logs, specifically related to IT support. This data is stored in a traditional SQL server and is exported into CSV or Microsoft Excel formats. The data is:&#xA;Well-structured, divided into specific columns The designated column for embedding and storing in a vector database includes the call resolution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining Embedding Model and VectorStore with FAISS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/define_embed_model_n_vector_with_faiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:27:58 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/define_embed_model_n_vector_with_faiss/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a little surprising to me that Facebook AI Similarity Search (FAISS) was released in 2017. An explanation from its official documentation:&#xA;&amp;hellip; FAISS, a library that allows us to quickly search for multimedia documents that are similar to each other - a challenge where traditional query search engines fall short. We’ve built nearest-neighbor search implementations for billion-scale data sets that are some 8.5x faster than the previous reported state-of-the-art, along with the fastest k-selection algorithm on the GPU known in the literature.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complete Code</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/complete_code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:33:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/complete_code/</guid>
      <description>Load pretty print library and ignore some annoying UserWarning message. These are optional steps.&#xA;from pprint import pprint from warnings import filterwarnings filterwarnings(&amp;#34;ignore&amp;#34;, category=UserWarning) Remember to create reranker_sample.csv, according to the sample provided in Appendix in this chapter. And place it in the same directory of this code.&#xA;Use CSVLoader to load the CSV file and include only the specified columns in the page_content of each Document. Note that any columns not listed under metadata_columns will be included in page_content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:34:02 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/summary/</guid>
      <description>In this chapter, we covered several key concepts and techniques:&#xA;We learned how to utilize the CSVLoader to efficiently load data from CSV files, enhancing the performance of our chatbot by ensuring that selected information is communicated effectively with the retriever. We continued to adhere to the Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) process, which involves retrieving relevant information from the context to generate responses to questions. We used HuggingFaceEndpoint to manage and orchestrate the Mistral LLM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appendix</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/appendix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 21:35:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/langchain_project_book/ticketing_sys/appendix/</guid>
      <description>The reranker.csv sample file&#xA;ticket_number,date,caller,application,query,responder,solution,timestamp 000001,2024-04-01,John Doe,Windows Operating System,&amp;#34;I&amp;#39;m having trouble logging into my account. I keep getting an error message saying my password is incorrect, even though I know I&amp;#39;m entering it correctly.&amp;#34;,Jane Smith,&amp;#34;Verified the user&amp;#39;s account information and reset their password. Provided step-by-step instructions on how to log in with the new password.&amp;#34;,2024-04-01 10:15:23 000002,2024-03-30,Jane Doe,Mobile Device,&amp;#34;I placed an order last week but it still hasn&amp;#39;t arrived. I need to know the status of my order.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
